hey everybody and welcome back to three
questions with the alliance for Mission
and renewal and today I have two of my
favorites my own people from my own
church Ally and Linda you want to
introduce yourselves everybody yeah
great hi I'm Linda Lloyd I'm Ally viny
and we're the women's ministry
coordinators at Chesterfield
Presbyterian Church yes and tell us are
you do other people live with you Ali
and Linda yes yes yes I have a husband
Tim and I have two daughters Lindsay and
Lippy and how long have you been married
Linda oh oh you're gonna make me think I
think 37 years 37 years a long
time Alie yeah so I'm married to Drew um
and he works at covenant Seminary so
that's a fun we're a very PCA couple
when people meet us PCA that's right
very P You're All In yes we come across
very very Christian um and then I have
three kids that are um two four and six
okay great I'm going to ask you are
three questions and the first one is
just tell us about your little corner of
the kingdom and what you do there at
Chesterfield yes yes so uh like I said
we're the women's ministry coordinators
and um we just love the women here Ally
and I work together on this it's a it's
a big job but we love it um some of our
main things we do um we choose and
coordinate and run um eight Bible study
women's Bible studies each semester
which we love and train the leaders pick
out the materials um discipleship is a
big thing here that we love that uh we
do uh form groups train and uh follow
through with them um uh as they go along
on their Journey um we have Gatherings
and support for young moms that we think
is very important to support them and to
bring them together also moms that are
launching their kids so we try to to
bring them together and uh and uh make
that connection there with them uh we
have little quiet mini Retreats so that
people can kind of take time to reflect
um we have many Community Building dis
Gatherings and fun things and uh our
main thing is just to connect women we
just love that connection that we can
make with them with us with each other
and to the Lord and just to kind of walk
alongside them and that that's just the
greatest job ever yeah so that's not
much not much going on over there not
just a name a few you got me with eight
Bible
studies so tell us in in all that what's
going on tell us a story about how
you've seen God at work through this
ministry of yours together yeah so I
would say one of the things we were like
most excited about and most proud of is
our discipleship
program um and so we we really spent a
lot of time we started it we launched it
in
2018 um and it was I I had my first kid
that year and we joked that it was my um
I had two babies that
winter and it's debatable which was
harder I
discipleship might have been harder um
and so we set it up so that it's a
two-year commitment and um it's groups
of like three women that meet together
on their own
time and um in the first year they go
through the spiritual disciplines um and
they do like two disciplines a week and
then the second year they um learn the
sore method of inductive Bible study um
and they go through Galatians and learn
how to do an indu a Bible study or add
to their knowledge that they already are
bringing to the table um and so we have
just loved seeing those groups go
through that program they have uh the
feedback that we have gotten has just
been so sweet of like um one how they've
grown in the relationship with the Lord
um have theyve seen like this consistent
time and like um intentional time that
they've spent with the Lord just how
that's grown their relationship um and
then the time that they've spent
together
processing that together learning from
each other growing with each other um
really being in each other's lives for
two years where they're meeting pretty
much weekly or bi-weekly um and they're
really bearing one another's burdens
they're praying with each other they're
in each other's business in a good way
you know yeah just the sweetness of that
and how um they just come away just
being like wow I didn't think I would
learn that much I didn't think I would
grow that much the Holy Spirit has just
been teaching me so many new things and
applying different things and you know
taking this thing from this place and um
just how the Holy Spirit does that so
it's just been such a sweet thing to see
all that hard work that we put into it
really bear so much good fruit in our
women it's just been such a fun sweet
encouraging thing with I mean because
you know it's hard there's hard things
with all for sure so when so when Jesus
said go and make disciples this you took
them seriously this is your version of
likeing we're trying our best this is
what we're doing it yeah yeah yeah it's
wonderful it's wonderful to hear such a
such a purposeful discipleship going
through it's so how how can we your
brothers and sisters out here in the
PCA encourage you enable you help you to
keep doing what you're doing yeah yeah I
think so something I've seen I so I went
to Seminary and um so I have a degree
from covenant in um so a lot of my
friends also have degrees and they're
paid staff but then I have other friends
especially in like the St Lewis or
whatever area that I just have some
networks where they're volunteer staff
and I just think that's so hard for them
it's like they because so much of my
life is like this is women's ministry
like this is my life like I I raise my
kids and I do women's ministry and and I
try to be a good neighbor and I try you
know like I care about the people around
me but so much much of my energy and
time goes into this job and so I just
can't imagine doing this job as a notp
paid staff person I just like it's such
a big job I mean women are half of the
adult population of any church and so or
more yeah or more not more and so to not
pay a staff to not pay someone to
Shepherd
this this part of your church it just
that makes me sad and so I I really do
feel for um the women I know who are
doing this on a volunteer basis and I
know it's hard I know there's a lot of
of every church and so but I just think
prioritizing having a paid staff person
right is um is really important right
because volunteers are important but
this is a big Ministry and it it's a you
know it's a vital part of the church and
so it it is a big deal so and you and
you guys do this together which is such
a great model and so helpful I couldn't
recomend more I don't know do without
each other yeah it's um it's it's just
really great to to what we each bring to
the table but just what we can do
together is so much stronger than on our
own it's just good to have that support
system so that we can support others so
and just different Generations different
styles different gifts different
personalities I mean God uses it all and
it's it's just been a beautiful thing to
be a part
of thank you guys thank you for what you
do for loving me and all the other
Chesterfield thank you we're thankful
for you we're so glad that you're here
with us too we really love you your gift
as well what a gift yes yes thanks for
talking to us yeah well have a good one
thank you you too